(Mrs Koothrappali:)Rajesh, do you remember Lalita Gupta?
(Raj:)The little fat girl that used to kick me
in the samosas and call me untouchable?
(Mrs Koothrappali:)Yes. Well, now she's
a dental student at USC...
(Mrs Koothrappali:)...so we gave her
your contact information.
(Raj:)Why did you do that?
(Dr Koothrappali:)You're 26 years old, Rajesh.
We want grandchildren.
- But, Papa, I'm not supposed...
- Lalita's parents approved the match.
(Dr Koothrappali:)If you decide on a spring wedding,
we can avoid monsoon season.
A spring wedding?
It's up to you. We don't want to meddle.
(Raj:)If you don't want to meddle,
why are you meddling?
(Dr Koothrappali:)Your parents
don't consider this meddling.
(Sheldon:)While arranged marriages
are no longer the norm...
(Sheldon:)...Indian parents continue to have
an involvement in their children's love lives.
(Raj:)Why are you telling me
about my own culture?
(Sheldon:)You seemed confused.
- Sorry, but with all due respect, I don't...
- I'm sorry, darling. We have to go.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)Doogie Howser is on.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)Grandma, it's Doogie time.
- Bye-bye.